this is 
some > kind
of & test text.
simple
for < the
testing purpose
.

SharePoint is a web-based collaborative platform that integrates with Microsoft Office. Launched in 2001,[5] SharePoint is primarily sold as a document management and storage system, but the product is highly configurable and usage varies substantially among organizations.

Microsoft states that SharePoint has 190 million users across 200,000 customer organizations.[6]

这是一些测试文字，还有一些中文标点《》